chances are you've probably already
heard of Teemu well some of the prices
are just insanely cheap a portable
washing machine was nine dollars now I'm
not very smart but how is that possible
so I got this product the portable
washing machine and a few other ones
Let's test them out and see if they're
any good it doesn't have a fill line so
I'm just gonna go for it this is like
four pair of underwear right here put
some of my natural laundry detergent in
there put it on standard washing I'll
see you guys in like 10 minutes while
that's washing I got a couple other
things too like this game console that
has like 400 games on it let's see if I
can play it while I'm watching the
screen
huh
nope okay it says it's all done I'm
gonna drain it out by pulling the
plunger here and next step is the drying
option this thing comes with so I mean
gosh I didn't know what to expect from
temu I have to give them credit for
actually being an affordable company
with good quality products so if you
want it I would act fast because nine
dollars is crazy